(Sheldon:)Four hours more and we would have
closed down the HomeTown Buffet.
- I thought you had plans with Amy.
- Yeah, I did.
(Sheldon:)But then Wil called Amy a pain in the A-S-S.
(Sheldon:)She got huffy and left,
and then Wil and I headed out to dinner.
(Sheldon:)That place really did remind me
of my hometown.
(Sheldon:)Because there we also have
a HomeTown Buffet.
- Hold on. Wil and Amy had an argument?
- Yes, quite the kerfuffle.
- Then Amy got mad and left?
- Walked right out the door.
(Leonard:)And you?
(Sheldon:)Enjoyed a delightful dinner
at a reasonable price.
(Sheldon:)The manager recognized Wil and let us sit
right next to the frozen-yogurt machine.
(Sheldon:)Right next to it.
(Sheldon:)I was closer to it than I am to you right now.
- Buddy, I think Amy might be upset.
- Why's that?
(Leonard:)Because your friend was rude to her
and then you went to dinner with him.
(Sheldon:)You're just repeating what I said.